Styles Carnley

206.605.6120 I styles.carnley@gmail.com

Dedicated technical expert with experience providing support in a 450+ user environment. Skilled problem-solver able to communicate well with users at all levels of proficiency. Troubleshoot, resolve and document help requests for desktop, laptop, mobile, network, AV, telecommunications and peripheral devices.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Technical Troubleshooting & Repair
- End User Guidance & Training
- Vendor/Client Management
- Research & Consultation

- System Upgrades & Optimization
- Backup & Recovery Solutions
- Technical & User Documentation
- IT Procurement & Inventory Management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Computer Technician Contractor | HELLOTECH, Lansing, MI & Seattle/Tacoma, WA | 2018 - Present

Provide Tier 1 and 2 technical support for in-home and small business users. Ensure day-of resolution focusing on computer support and repair, POS systems, home networks, smart home devices and TV's.

- Consistently achieve a user satisfaction rating of 4.8/5.0 (16% higher than average)
- Commended for quickly resolving complex issues including home and business systems, AV devices, system crashes, connectivity problems, and data recovery

IT Support Consultant | Arrow Self-Storage, Howell, MI | 2017 - 2019

Provided new business owner with consultation and critical technical support of desktop, laptop, security gate and camera environments, both in-person and remotely.

- Saved company \$9000 by reconfiguring and repairing the security gate system and database
- Proactively designed and implemented a central inventory system that maintained and catalogued computer devices, end-of-life-cycle, and warranties
- Created standard operating procedures and instruction manuals for owner and employees

Computer Support Specialist II | University of Washington, Seattle, WA | 2015 - 2017

Provided help desk support for students, faculty and staff in a department with 500+ devices and 50+ Servers. Maintenance of datacenter environment, virtualization, clustering, SAN, remote access, and Backup disaster recovery.

- Co-led implementation of LEAN practices for increased efficiency, including launching a new ticketing system, updating workflow, re-organizing department, and leading group trainings
- Reduced wait-time for complex incident ticket resolution from one week to one day
- Nominated for Employee of the Year within 6 months of employment for excellent support

Styles Carnley

206.605.6120 I styles.carnley@gmail.com

Network Specialist Assistant | University of Washington, Seattle, WA | 2014 - 2015

Provided support of all physical elements pertaining to voice and data to the UW community.

- Increased efficiency with wiping and surplus of network switches
- Installed configurations on Juniper switches for tech refresh projects
- Coordinated repair & replacement of RMA network switches, routers, phones, and UPS devices
- Maintained accurate inventory records, ordering parts, and organized parts and equipment

IT Support Specialist | Center for Human Services, Seattle, WA | 2013 - 2015

Provided helpdesk support for non-profit agency staff, both on-site and remotely at multiple locations. Troubleshoot, resolve & document help requests for desktop, laptop, mobile, network and peripherals.

- Customized a training program to help employees gain essential technical skills, including HIPAA compliance as it relates to technology
- Maintained, built, and deployed Windows OS (Windows XP, 7 & 8, Windows Server 2003/2008)
- Performed break/fix, installations, and upgrades of computers, mobile devices, and peripherals
- Received Diversity Award for excellence in supporting staff and administration with awareness
- Responsible for Windows Administration on Windows Server 2003/2008

Computer Technician I | InterConnection, Seattle, WA | 2012 - 2013

Responsible for desktop and laptop repair at refurbishing nonprofit for low-income households and Nonprofits. Applied and held quality control standards, used software to perform stress tests on hardware.

- Recruited and hired within 3 months of volunteering
- Diagnosed hardware issues; replaced memory, optical, hard drives, power supplies, laptop screens, keyboards, and video/sound cards
- Responsible for quality control: building/installing images, updates, drivers & testing for errors

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (BS): Software Development | Western Governors University | Expected 12/22

TECHNICAL SUMMARY

Certification: ITIL V4 Certification, CIW Site Development Associate, CIW User Interface Designer

Platforms: Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, iOS, Android

Networking: LANs/WANs/SANs, TCP/IP, VoIP, DNS, HTTP, Wireless/VPN Architecture

Hardware: iPads, iMacs, tablets, desktops, laptops, printers, scanners, projectors, AV devices

Applications: Microsoft Office 365, SCCM, VMware: VSphere Horizon, Jira, Paper Cut